{
  "$schema": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nickwang0808/flash-card/master/schema/cards.schema.json",
  "我": {
    "back": "I / me",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-20T04:17:18.194Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:17:18.194Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T04:16:54.347Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:16:54.347Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>我<rt>wǒ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "你": {
    "back": "you",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T04:16:27.502Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:16:27.502Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T04:17:09.698Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:17:09.698Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>你<rt>nǐ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "他": {
    "back": "he / him",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T17:45:45.889Z",
      "stability": 1.85817869,
      "difficulty": 7.48632926,
      "elapsed_days": 1,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 4,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:45:45.889Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-20T04:18:09.652Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:18:09.652Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>他<rt>tā</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "她": {
    "back": "she / her",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-20T04:17:29.618Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:17:29.618Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-20T04:18:13.680Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:18:13.680Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>她<rt>tā</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "我们": {
    "back": "we / us",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-20T04:17:59.222Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:17:59.222Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-20T04:18:22.669Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-16T04:18:22.669Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>我<rt>wǒ</rt></ruby><ruby>们<rt>men</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "你们": {
    "back": "you (plural)",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-21T17:56:01.845Z",
      "stability": 3.75145221,
      "difficulty": 6.02202219,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 3,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:56:01.845Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T17:49:25.843Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:49:25.843Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>你<rt>nǐ</rt></ruby><ruby>们<rt>men</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "他们": {
    "back": "they / them",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-21T17:45:23.725Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:45:23.725Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T17:49:40.290Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:49:40.290Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>他<rt>tā</rt></ruby><ruby>们<rt>men</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "这": {
    "back": "this",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-21T17:45:35.949Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:45:35.949Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T17:49:48.816Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:49:48.816Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>这<rt>zhè</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "那": {
    "back": "that",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "pronouns"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:17:52.148Z",
      "stability": 0.01407771,
      "difficulty": 9.84246312,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 14,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:17:52.148Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:26:40.836Z",
      "stability": 0.08820147,
      "difficulty": 9.26736216,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 7,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:16:40.836Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>那<rt>nà</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "谁": {
    "back": "who",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "question-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:45:54.333Z",
      "stability": 0.5666983,
      "difficulty": 7.17663617,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:45:54.333Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:18:37.517Z",
      "stability": 0.01407771,
      "difficulty": 9.76490354,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 11,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:18:37.517Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>谁<rt>shéi</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "什么": {
    "back": "what",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "question-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:07:53.558Z",
      "stability": 0.10502158,
      "difficulty": 9.17912912,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 6,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:07:53.558Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:27:26.545Z",
      "stability": 0.14784636,
      "difficulty": 9.12091584,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 7,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:17:26.545Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>什<rt>shén</rt></ruby><ruby>么<rt>me</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "哪": {
    "back": "which",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "question-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:28:08.856Z",
      "stability": 0.01,
      "difficulty": 9.79799444,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 11,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:18:08.856Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:10:31.540Z",
      "stability": 0.01789222,
      "difficulty": 9.50348826,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 7,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:10:31.540Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>哪<rt>nǎ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "哪儿": {
    "back": "where",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "question-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:52:56.903Z",
      "stability": 0.28393201,
      "difficulty": 8.06044885,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 3,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:52:56.903Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:18:54.943Z",
      "stability": 0.01407771,
      "difficulty": 9.76490354,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 11,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:18:54.943Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>哪<rt>nǎ</rt></ruby><ruby>儿<rt>r</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "几": {
    "back": "how many (small numbers) / what (time)",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "question-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:19:10.727Z",
      "stability": 0.01407771,
      "difficulty": 9.6769825,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 10,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:19:10.727Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:11:41.630Z",
      "stability": 0.20026676,
      "difficulty": 8.58493344,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 5,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:11:41.630Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>几<rt>jǐ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "多少": {
    "back": "how many / how much",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "question-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:17:58.649Z",
      "stability": 0.01407771,
      "difficulty": 9.59534684,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 9,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:17:58.649Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:07:22.492Z",
      "stability": 0.39971132,
      "difficulty": 7.97036948,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 4,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:07:22.492Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>多<rt>duō</rt></ruby><ruby>少<rt>shao</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "怎么": {
    "back": "how / why",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "question-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:26:50.254Z",
      "stability": 0.01,
      "difficulty": 9.70680108,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 9,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:16:50.254Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:28:46.540Z",
      "stability": 0.01261999,
      "difficulty": 9.60490779,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 9,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:18:46.540Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>怎<rt>zěn</rt></ruby><ruby>么<rt>me</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "怎么样": {
    "back": "how is it / how about",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "question-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:10:58.340Z",
      "stability": 0.20026676,
      "difficulty": 8.58493344,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 5,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:10:58.340Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:27:06.977Z",
      "stability": 0.02999155,
      "difficulty": 9.3883949,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 7,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:17:06.977Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>怎<rt>zěn</rt></ruby><ruby>么<rt>me</rt></ruby><ruby>样<rt>yàng</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "零": {
    "back": "zero",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:46:55.334Z",
      "stability": 0.5666983,
      "difficulty": 7.17663617,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:46:55.334Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T17:50:18.893Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:50:18.893Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>零<rt>líng</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "一": {
    "back": "one",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-20T17:42:15.784Z",
      "stability": 3.32446519,
      "difficulty": 7.58928184,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 3,
      "reps": 4,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:42:15.784Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T17:50:25.276Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:50:25.276Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>一<rt>yī</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "二": {
    "back": "two",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T17:49:20.211Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:49:20.211Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:56:09.124Z",
      "stability": 0.83500911,
      "difficulty": 7.58754857,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 3,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:56:09.124Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>二<rt>èr</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "三": {
    "back": "three",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-21T17:41:13.125Z",
      "stability": 3.87213004,
      "difficulty": 7.15845635,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 3,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:41:13.125Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T17:50:37.700Z",
      "stability": 1.66658995,
      "difficulty": 6.47329177,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 2,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:50:37.700Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>三<rt>sān</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "四": {
    "back": "four",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:17:14.307Z",
      "stability": 0.01407771,
      "difficulty": 9.65103529,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 9,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:17:14.307Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:29:01.987Z",
      "stability": 0.02214118,
      "difficulty": 9.59730012,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 9,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:19:01.987Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>四<rt>sì</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "五": {
    "back": "five",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:03:11.706Z",
      "stability": 0.23845785,
      "difficulty": 8.34644611,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 4,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:03:11.706Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:49:14.607Z",
      "stability": 0.5666983,
      "difficulty": 7.17663617,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:49:14.607Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>五<rt>wǔ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "六": {
    "back": "six",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:03:24.708Z",
      "stability": 0.23845785,
      "difficulty": 8.34644611,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 4,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:03:24.708Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:56:23.737Z",
      "stability": 0.83500911,
      "difficulty": 7.58754857,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 3,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:56:23.737Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>六<rt>liù</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "七": {
    "back": "seven",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:26:55.032Z",
      "stability": 0.01,
      "difficulty": 9.79056674,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 16,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 3,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:16:55.032Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:28:24.940Z",
      "stability": 0.02214117,
      "difficulty": 9.60149799,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 9,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:18:24.940Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>七<rt>qī</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "八": {
    "back": "eight",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:47:27.783Z",
      "stability": 0.5666983,
      "difficulty": 7.17663617,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:47:27.783Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:14:55.134Z",
      "stability": 0.04419146,
      "difficulty": 9.47982333,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 8,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:14:55.134Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>八<rt>bā</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "九": {
    "back": "nine",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-21T17:41:38.330Z",
      "stability": 3.87213004,
      "difficulty": 7.15845635,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 3,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:41:38.330Z"
    },
    "reverseState": {
      "due": "2026-02-17T18:28:32.604Z",
      "stability": 0.04419145,
      "difficulty": 9.46115053,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 8,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 1,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:18:32.604Z"
    },
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>九<rt>jiǔ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "十": {
    "front": "<ruby>十<rt>shí</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "ten",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  "两": {
    "back": "two (used with measure words)",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "numbers"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:01:14.195Z",
      "stability": 0.18392427,
      "difficulty": 9.25651936,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 9,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:01:14.195Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>两<rt>liǎng</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "年": {
    "front": "<ruby>年<rt>nián</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "year",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "月": {
    "front": "<ruby>月<rt>yuè</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "month",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "日": {
    "front": "<ruby>日<rt>rì</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "day (formal) / date",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "星期": {
    "front": "<ruby>星<rt>xīng</rt></ruby><ruby>期<rt>qī</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "week",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "今天": {
    "front": "<ruby>今<rt>jīn</rt></ruby><ruby>天<rt>tiān</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "today",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "明天": {
    "front": "<ruby>明<rt>míng</rt></ruby><ruby>天<rt>tiān</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "tomorrow",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "昨天": {
    "front": "<ruby>昨<rt>zuó</rt></ruby><ruby>天<rt>tiān</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "yesterday",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "上午": {
    "back": "morning (before noon)",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:44:47.042Z",
      "stability": 0.2146647,
      "difficulty": 9.54151247,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 15,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:44:47.042Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>上<rt>shàng</rt></ruby><ruby>午<rt>wǔ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "中午": {
    "back": "noon",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:44:23.474Z",
      "stability": 0.60777935,
      "difficulty": 8.9111157,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 8,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:44:23.474Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>中<rt>zhōng</rt></ruby><ruby>午<rt>wǔ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "下午": {
    "back": "afternoon",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:44:55.947Z",
      "stability": 0.12445305,
      "difficulty": 9.62482395,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 16,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:44:55.947Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>下<rt>xià</rt></ruby><ruby>午<rt>wǔ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "时候": {
    "front": "<ruby>时<rt>shí</rt></ruby><ruby>候<rt>hou</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "time / moment",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "现在": {
    "front": "<ruby>现<rt>xiàn</rt></ruby><ruby>在<rt>zài</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "now",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "点": {
    "front": "<ruby>点<rt>diǎn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "o'clock / point",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  "爸爸": {
    "front": "<ruby>爸<rt>bà</rt></ruby><ruby>爸<rt>ba</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "dad",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  "妈妈": {
    "front": "<ruby>妈<rt>mā</rt></ruby><ruby>妈<rt>ma</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "mom",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  "儿子": {
    "front": "<ruby>儿<rt>ér</rt></ruby><ruby>子<rt>zi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "son",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  "女儿": {
    "front": "<ruby>女<rt>nǚ</rt></ruby><ruby>儿<rt>ér</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "daughter",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  "家": {
    "front": "<ruby>家<rt>jiā</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "home / family",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  "先生": {
    "front": "<ruby>先<rt>xiān</rt></ruby><ruby>生<rt>sheng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "Mr. / sir / husband",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  "小姐": {
    "front": "<ruby>小<rt>xiǎo</rt></ruby><ruby>姐<rt>jiě</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "Miss / young lady",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  "人": {
    "front": "<ruby>人<rt>rén</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "person / people",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  "朋友": {
    "front": "<ruby>朋<rt>péng</rt></ruby><ruby>友<rt>you</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "friend",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  "同学": {
    "front": "<ruby>同<rt>tóng</rt></ruby><ruby>学<rt>xué</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "classmate",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  "老师": {
    "front": "<ruby>老<rt>lǎo</rt></ruby><ruby>师<rt>shī</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "teacher",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  "学生": {
    "front": "<ruby>学<rt>xué</rt></ruby><ruby>生<rt>shēng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "student",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  "医生": {
    "front": "<ruby>医<rt>yī</rt></ruby><ruby>生<rt>shēng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "doctor",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  "学校": {
    "front": "<ruby>学<rt>xué</rt></ruby><ruby>校<rt>xiào</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "school",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "places"
    ]
  },
  "医院": {
    "front": "<ruby>医<rt>yī</rt></ruby><ruby>院<rt>yuàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "hospital",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "places"
    ]
  },
  "商店": {
    "front": "<ruby>商<rt>shāng</rt></ruby><ruby>店<rt>diàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "store / shop",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "places"
    ]
  },
  "饭店": {
    "front": "<ruby>饭<rt>fàn</rt></ruby><ruby>店<rt>diàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "restaurant / hotel",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "places"
    ]
  },
  "中国": {
    "back": "China",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "places"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T22:44:47.169Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-15T22:44:47.169Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>中<rt>zhōng</rt></ruby><ruby>国<rt>guó</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "北京": {
    "front": "<ruby>北<rt>běi</rt></ruby><ruby>京<rt>jīng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "Beijing",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "places"
    ]
  },
  "水": {
    "front": "<ruby>水<rt>shuǐ</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "water",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "food-drink"
    ]
  },
  "茶": {
    "front": "<ruby>茶<rt>chá</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "tea",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "food-drink"
    ]
  },
  "米饭": {
    "front": "<ruby>米<rt>mǐ</rt></ruby><ruby>饭<rt>fàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "cooked rice",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "food-drink"
    ]
  },
  "菜": {
    "front": "<ruby>菜<rt>cài</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "dish / vegetable",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "food-drink"
    ]
  },
  "水果": {
    "front": "<ruby>水<rt>shuǐ</rt></ruby><ruby>果<rt>guǒ</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "fruit",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "food-drink"
    ]
  },
  "苹果": {
    "front": "<ruby>苹<rt>píng</rt></ruby><ruby>果<rt>guǒ</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "apple",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "food-drink"
    ]
  },
  "杯子": {
    "front": "<ruby>杯<rt>bēi</rt></ruby><ruby>子<rt>zi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "cup / glass",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "food-drink"
    ]
  },
  "书": {
    "back": "book",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:51:49.609Z",
      "stability": 0.39971132,
      "difficulty": 8.57944474,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 6,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:51:49.609Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>书<rt>shū</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "字": {
    "front": "<ruby>字<rt>zì</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "character / word",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "桌子": {
    "front": "<ruby>桌<rt>zhuō</rt></ruby><ruby>子<rt>zi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "table / desk",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "椅子": {
    "front": "<ruby>椅<rt>yǐ</rt></ruby><ruby>子<rt>zi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "chair",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "电话": {
    "front": "<ruby>电<rt>diàn</rt></ruby><ruby>话<rt>huà</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "telephone",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "电脑": {
    "front": "<ruby>电<rt>diàn</rt></ruby><ruby>脑<rt>nǎo</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "computer",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "电视": {
    "front": "<ruby>电<rt>diàn</rt></ruby><ruby>视<rt>shì</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "television",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "电影": {
    "front": "<ruby>电<rt>diàn</rt></ruby><ruby>影<rt>yǐng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "movie / film",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "钱": {
    "front": "<ruby>钱<rt>qián</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "money",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "衣服": {
    "front": "<ruby>衣<rt>yī</rt></ruby><ruby>服<rt>fu</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "clothes",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "东西": {
    "back": "thing / stuff",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:12:00.919Z",
      "stability": 0.02978006,
      "difficulty": 9.62933152,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 12,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:12:00.919Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>东<rt>dōng</rt></ruby><ruby>西<rt>xi</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "猫": {
    "front": "<ruby>猫<rt>māo</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "cat",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "狗": {
    "front": "<ruby>狗<rt>gǒu</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "dog",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "名字": {
    "front": "<ruby>名<rt>míng</rt></ruby><ruby>字<rt>zi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "name",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "汉语": {
    "front": "<ruby>汉<rt>hàn</rt></ruby><ruby>语<rt>yǔ</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "Chinese language",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "天气": {
    "front": "<ruby>天<rt>tiān</rt></ruby><ruby>气<rt>qì</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "weather",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "objects"
    ]
  },
  "飞机": {
    "front": "<ruby>飞<rt>fēi</rt></ruby><ruby>机<rt>jī</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "airplane",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "transport"
    ]
  },
  "出租车": {
    "front": "<ruby>出<rt>chū</rt></ruby><ruby>租<rt>zū</rt></ruby><ruby>车<rt>chē</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "taxi",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "transport"
    ]
  },
  "车站": {
    "front": "<ruby>车<rt>chē</rt></ruby><ruby>站<rt>zhàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "station (bus/train)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "transport"
    ]
  },
  "是": {
    "front": "<ruby>是<rt>shì</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to be (am/is/are)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "有": {
    "front": "<ruby>有<rt>yǒu</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to have / there is",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "看": {
    "front": "<ruby>看<rt>kàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to look / to watch / to read",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "听": {
    "front": "<ruby>听<rt>tīng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to listen",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "说": {
    "front": "<ruby>说<rt>shuō</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to speak / to say",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "读": {
    "front": "<ruby>读<rt>dú</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to read (aloud)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "写": {
    "front": "<ruby>写<rt>xiě</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to write",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "想": {
    "front": "<ruby>想<rt>xiǎng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to think / to want / to miss",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "去": {
    "front": "<ruby>去<rt>qù</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to go",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "来": {
    "front": "<ruby>来<rt>lái</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to come",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "回": {
    "front": "<ruby>回<rt>huí</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to return / to go back",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "吃": {
    "front": "<ruby>吃<rt>chī</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to eat",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "喝": {
    "front": "<ruby>喝<rt>hē</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to drink",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "睡觉": {
    "front": "<ruby>睡<rt>shuì</rt></ruby><ruby>觉<rt>jiào</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to sleep",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "买": {
    "back": "to buy",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:00:53.944Z",
      "stability": 0.39971132,
      "difficulty": 8.57780292,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 6,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:00:53.944Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>买<rt>mǎi</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "做": {
    "front": "<ruby>做<rt>zuò</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to do / to make",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "住": {
    "front": "<ruby>住<rt>zhù</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to live / to stay",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "坐": {
    "front": "<ruby>坐<rt>zuò</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to sit / to take (transport)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "开": {
    "front": "<ruby>开<rt>kāi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to open / to drive",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "学习": {
    "front": "<ruby>学<rt>xué</rt></ruby><ruby>习<rt>xí</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to study / to learn",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "工作": {
    "front": "<ruby>工<rt>gōng</rt></ruby><ruby>作<rt>zuò</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to work / job",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "打电话": {
    "front": "<ruby>打<rt>dǎ</rt></ruby><ruby>电<rt>diàn</rt></ruby><ruby>话<rt>huà</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to make a phone call",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "看见": {
    "front": "<ruby>看<rt>kàn</rt></ruby><ruby>见<rt>jiàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to see",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "会": {
    "front": "<ruby>会<rt>huì</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "can (learned skill) / will",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "能": {
    "front": "<ruby>能<rt>néng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "can / able to",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "认识": {
    "front": "<ruby>认<rt>rèn</rt></ruby><ruby>识<rt>shi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to know (a person) / to recognize",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "知道": {
    "front": "<ruby>知<rt>zhī</rt></ruby><ruby>道<rt>dào</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to know (a fact)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "喜欢": {
    "front": "<ruby>喜<rt>xǐ</rt></ruby><ruby>欢<rt>huan</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to like",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "爱": {
    "front": "<ruby>爱<rt>ài</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to love",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "叫": {
    "front": "<ruby>叫<rt>jiào</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "to be called / to call",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "请": {
    "front": "<ruby>请<rt>qǐng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "please / to invite",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  "下雨": {
    "back": "to rain",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "verbs"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:51:40.088Z",
      "stability": 0.28393201,
      "difficulty": 8.63973185,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 5,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:51:40.088Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>下<rt>xià</rt></ruby><ruby>雨<rt>yǔ</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "你好": {
    "front": "<ruby>你<rt>nǐ</rt></ruby><ruby>好<rt>hǎo</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "hello",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  "谢谢": {
    "front": "<ruby>谢<rt>xiè</rt></ruby><ruby>谢<rt>xie</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "thank you",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  "不客气": {
    "back": "you're welcome",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "greetings"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:41:27.942Z",
      "stability": 1.33190575,
      "difficulty": 7.61448676,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 3,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:41:27.942Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>不<rt>bú</rt></ruby><ruby>客<rt>kè</rt></ruby><ruby>气<rt>qi</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "对不起": {
    "front": "<ruby>对<rt>duì</rt></ruby><ruby>不<rt>bu</rt></ruby><ruby>起<rt>qǐ</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "sorry",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  "没关系": {
    "front": "<ruby>没<rt>méi</rt></ruby><ruby>关<rt>guān</rt></ruby><ruby>系<rt>xi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "it's okay / no problem",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  "再见": {
    "front": "<ruby>再<rt>zài</rt></ruby><ruby>见<rt>jiàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "goodbye",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  "好": {
    "front": "<ruby>好<rt>hǎo</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "good / fine / okay",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "大": {
    "front": "<ruby>大<rt>dà</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "big / large",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "小": {
    "front": "<ruby>小<rt>xiǎo</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "small / little",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "多": {
    "front": "<ruby>多<rt>duō</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "many / much",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "少": {
    "front": "<ruby>少<rt>shǎo</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "few / little",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "冷": {
    "front": "<ruby>冷<rt>lěng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "cold",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "热": {
    "front": "<ruby>热<rt>rè</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "hot",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "高兴": {
    "front": "<ruby>高<rt>gāo</rt></ruby><ruby>兴<rt>xìng</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "happy / glad",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "漂亮": {
    "front": "<ruby>漂<rt>piào</rt></ruby><ruby>亮<rt>liang</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "beautiful / pretty",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "高": {
    "front": "<ruby>高<rt>gāo</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "tall / high",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "对": {
    "front": "<ruby>对<rt>duì</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "correct / right",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adjectives"
    ]
  },
  "不": {
    "back": "not / no",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adverbs"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-19T22:43:37.825Z",
      "stability": 4.46685806,
      "difficulty": 5.27296793,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 2,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-15T22:43:37.825Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>不<rt>bù</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "没": {
    "front": "<ruby>没<rt>méi</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "not (negates 有) / have not",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adverbs"
    ]
  },
  "很": {
    "front": "<ruby>很<rt>hěn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "very",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adverbs"
    ]
  },
  "太": {
    "front": "<ruby>太<rt>tài</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "too (excessively)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adverbs"
    ]
  },
  "都": {
    "front": "<ruby>都<rt>dōu</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "all / both",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adverbs"
    ]
  },
  "也": {
    "back": "also / too",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adverbs"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:08:36.940Z",
      "stability": 0.01407771,
      "difficulty": 9.74349167,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 13,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:08:36.940Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>也<rt>yě</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "和": {
    "front": "<ruby>和<rt>hé</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "and / with",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adverbs"
    ]
  },
  "在": {
    "front": "<ruby>在<rt>zài</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "at / in / to be at",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "adverbs"
    ]
  },
  "的": {
    "front": "<ruby>的<rt>de</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "possessive / descriptive particle (my, your, big one, etc.)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "particles"
    ]
  },
  "了": {
    "back": "completion particle (indicates action is done or situation changed)",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "particles"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": false,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T18:01:29.564Z",
      "stability": 0.28192981,
      "difficulty": 8.94718913,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 8,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T18:01:29.564Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>了<rt>le</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "吗": {
    "front": "<ruby>吗<rt>ma</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "question particle (turns statement into yes/no question)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "particles"
    ]
  },
  "呢": {
    "front": "<ruby>呢<rt>ne</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "question particle (and you? / what about?)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "particles"
    ]
  },
  "个": {
    "back": "general measure word (most common classifier)",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "measure-words"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": false,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-21T17:43:29.821Z",
      "stability": 3.85782809,
      "difficulty": 7.84216213,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 4,
      "reps": 6,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:43:29.821Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>个<rt>gè</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "岁": {
    "front": "<ruby>岁<rt>suì</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "years old (age)",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "measure-words"
    ]
  },
  "块": {
    "front": "<ruby>块<rt>kuài</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "yuan (unit of money) / piece",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "measure-words"
    ]
  },
  "些": {
    "front": "<ruby>些<rt>xiē</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "some / a few",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "measure-words"
    ]
  },
  "里": {
    "front": "<ruby>里<rt>lǐ</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "inside / in",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "position"
    ]
  },
  "上": {
    "back": "up / on / above",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "position"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:42:44.549Z",
      "stability": 0.96908363,
      "difficulty": 8.2763649,
      "elapsed_days": 2,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 5,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:42:44.549Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>上<rt>shàng</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "下": {
    "back": "down / under / below",
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "position"
    ],
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "state": {
      "due": "2026-02-18T17:51:31.388Z",
      "stability": 0.28393201,
      "difficulty": 8.63973185,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 1,
      "reps": 5,
      "lapses": 1,
      "state": 2,
      "last_review": "2026-02-17T17:51:31.388Z"
    },
    "reverseState": null,
    "suspended": false,
    "front": "<ruby>下<rt>xià</rt></ruby>"
  },
  "前面": {
    "front": "<ruby>前<rt>qián</rt></ruby><ruby>面<rt>miàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "in front of / ahead",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "position"
    ]
  },
  "后面": {
    "front": "<ruby>后<rt>hòu</rt></ruby><ruby>面<rt>miàn</rt></ruby>",
    "back": "behind / at the back",
    "created": "2026-02-15T00:00:00.000Z",
    "reversible": true,
    "tags": [
      "hsk1",
      "position"
    ]
  }
}